It's cute, really.
可愛いね、本当に
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's not there, it's not there.
いないよ、いないよ
I can't stand it.
我慢できない
picture?
え?
Because people are coming.
人来るから
It's not coming.
来ないよ
Go where there is no one.
誰もいないところに行く
Yahoo.
やっほー
delicious?
おい しい?
He said he likes sweets.
甘いの好きって言ってたし
really like.
大好き
I ate crepes before too.
前もクレープ食べたしね
It was delicious.
美味しかった
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
How have you been lately?
最近どうなの?
There was an exam period recently, and I'm currently closed during the connection period.
最近は試験期間があって、今は接続期間中でお休みだけど、
The type that studies.
勉強してるタイプ
Oh, are you currently in the exam period?
あ、今試験期間中なの?
Oh, is that so?
あ、そうなの?
Oh no, then are you playing like that?
やばい、じゃあそんな遊んでる?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I have to study.
勉強しなきゃいけない
I'm studying now.
勉強してんだ、今
Are there any subjects you're good at?
何か得意科目とか?
I'm good at mathematics.
数学が得意
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだ
That's surprising.
意外だね
Are you not good at it?
苦手なの?
What I'm not good at is English.
苦手なのは英語
English?
英語?
weak point.
苦手
It's a science major.
理系なんだね
I want you to tell me, then.
教えて欲しいわ、じゃあ
Teach me to study.
勉強教えてよ
I have to teach you, though.
俺が教えなきゃいけないんだけどね、
Actually.
本当は
Is school fun?
学校楽しい?
fun.
楽しい
I haven't had much fun lately.
最近楽しいことなかったな
I went on a family trip.
家族旅行に行った
家族旅行行った
Family trip?
家族旅行?
Where did you go?
どこ行ったの?
It's a box.
箱ね
Did you take a hot spring?
温泉入ったの?
My skin feels so tight on the street.
通りでなんか お肌が 張りがあるよね
We're close, family.
仲いいんだね、家族ね
I've been feeling excited for the first time in a while.
久々、テンション上がっちゃったわ
Is there anything you want to see?
何か見たい物とかある?
hot spring?
温泉?
Clothes, food, etc.
お洋服とか 食べ物とか
food?
食べ物?
amazing!
すごい!
You're making progress, sweetie.
進んでるね、甘いもの
delicious!
おいしい!
good!
うまい!
delicious!
おい しい!
Isn't it a joint temperament?
関節気質じゃない?
I like this.
いいね、これ
Let's go, etc.
行こうか、いろいろ
There are a lot.
いっぱいある
I've been using this lately.
最近はこれ使ってる
What is that?
何それ?
Morning mask?
朝マスク?
Is it okay?
いいの?
This is really good.
これ めっちゃいい
Is it for shoulders?
肩用か
It's okay.
いいの
The flowers are beautiful, so that's why they're doing it.
お花綺麗だからやっぱそういうのやってるんだね
What is this?
これは何だろう?
When I apply this on my face, it gets really squishy.
これ顔に塗ったらめっちゃぷにぷに
Puni Puni?
ぷにぷに?
nice.
いいね
Maybe I should start too.
俺も始めようかな
Men's too.
メンズもね
Beautiful boy, I like it.
美容男子、いいね
Who is the beauty uncle?
美容おじさんは?
I also like hairdressers.
美容師さんも好き
TRUE?
本当?
I'll buy you whatever you want.
買ってあげるよ、欲しいやつ
let's see?
どれどれ?
this?
これ?
This is expensive.
高いよ、これ
This is 5,000 yuan.
5千元じゃん、これ
I'll buy it for you.
買ってあげるよ
thank you.
ありがとう
Are there about 10?
10本くらい、いる?
nice.
いいね
Shall we go somewhere?
いろいろ行こうか
It's cute, really.
可愛いね、本当ね
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
not present?
いない?
Can't resist?
我慢できない?
No.
ダメ
why?
なんで?
So, let's go somewhere where no one is around?
じゃあ、誰もいないとこ行く?
Was it delicious?
美味しかった?
It was delicious.
美味しかった
You drank it all.
全部飲んだね
I drank it all.
全部飲んだ
I was also able to buy cosmetics.
化粧品も買えたね
thank you.
ありがとう
it was fun?
楽しかった?
it was fun.
楽しかった
There was an aquarium.
水族館があったね
It's beautiful.
綺麗だね
I was thinking of going.
行こうかなと思ったんだけど
I wanted to go.
行きたかった
I wanted to go, but I thought I would enjoy it more.
行きたかったんだけど、 も っと楽しむかなと思って
I can't take it anymore.
もう、我慢できない
I'm amazing, I want to do it.
俺、すげえさ、 やりたいんだけどさ、
I heard that there is someone who really likes Mei-chan.
メイちゃんのことが すごい好きな人がいるんだって
I showed it to you.
俺、見せたんだけどさ
yes?
そう?
Did you show it to me?
見せちゃったの?
I was really excited and wanted to meet him.
なんかすごい興奮して、 会いたいみたいな感じで
Hey, okay?
ちょっと、 いい?
Read it.
読んで
Hello.
こんにちは
nice to meet you.
初めまして
Mei-chan, it's real.
メイちゃん、 本物だ
Soooo cute.
すっげえかわいい
That's terrible.
やばいね
Her skin is beautiful and smells great.
肌も綺麗だし、 しかもいい匂いする
I just saw it once and fell in love with it instantly.
一回見ただけでさ、 一瞬で好きになっちゃって、
I'm a fan.
ファンなんです
Fan?
フ ァン?
Is it okay?
いいの?
I was making all sorts of naughty noises.
いろいろエチの音しちゃって
TRUE?
本当?
Yay!
やったー
It's such a great style.
すごいスタイルいいよね
That's what I thought just by touching it.
ちょっと触っただけで 思ったんだけど
Soft.
柔らか
Mei-chan, this guy is so skinny,
メイちゃん、 こいつさ、細いのに、
It's big, or rather it feels good.
大きいというか、 いい感じだね
Does it hurt?
痛いの?
Does it feel good to be in pain?
痛いのが気持ちいいの?
Seriously?
マジで?
That's a pervert.
変態だね
It's good that it hurts.
痛いのがいいんだ
More like this.
こういうのより
Is it better like this?
こういう方がいいの?
How long does it hurt?
痛 いのってどれくらい?
Gyu.
ギューって
What is Gyu?
ギューって?
Is this good?
こういうのがいいの?
Wow, it's so wet.
うわ、すげー濡れてる
Look.
ほら
appear?
見える?
Look, here comes this person.
ほら、こんな人いっちゃって
Why did you get so wet?
どうしてこんな濡れちゃったの?
It's cute.
可愛いね
He looks me in the eyes when I'm kissing him.
キスしてるときに目を見てくれるのって
This is transparent.
透けてんだね、これ
Where is this touching you now?
これ今、どこ触られてんの?
That's naughty.
エッチだね
What about this?
こっちは?
point
分
That's right.
か ってるっすね
When I got my pants this wet, I went home.
こんなにパンツ濡れちゃったら、 帰り、
My pants are soaked though.
パンツビチョビチョだけど
Mei-chan, Mei-chan behind me.
メイちゃん、後ろのメイちゃん
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
It's cute that you're shy.
恥ずかしがってるの可愛いから
I'm putting in effort.
力入ってるよ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
I'm really tingling.
すげーヒクヒクしてる
Amazing asshole.
すごいお尻の穴
I'm tingling.
ヒクヒクしちゃってる
Mei-chan's important points are visible.
メイちゃんの大事なとこたる見え
hear?
聞こえる?
Why are you talking like this?
なんでこんなくしゃくしゃ言ってんの?
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
Isn't it because you feel it?
感じてるからじゃないの?
Does it feel good?
気 持ちいいの?
This is how I feel.
こう感じるんだね
A lot of naughty liquid is coming out.
エッチの液体いっぱい出てるんだけど
It feels good.
気持ちいいんだ
It's firmly in there.
しっかり入ってるよ
It's different from before, isn't it?
さっきとまた違うでしょ?
May
メイ
Chan, I had an expensive meal once.
ちゃん、 一度高くごはんしちゃった
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Do you know that the Sky Tree is here?
ここにスカイツリーあるの分かる?
I understand.
分かる
There's a Skytree over there though.
あそこにスカイツリーあるけどさ
This is my Sky Tree.
これ、俺のスカイツリー
Won't you make me feel so good?
これいっぱい気持ちよくしてくんない?
It feels good.
気持ちいいよ
That's amazing.
すごいね
I can go this far.
ここまでいけるね
It's cute.
可愛 いね